gameQuestions.txt

{question: "In which city can you find a famous ferris wheel featured in the movie Before Sunrise?", answer: "Vienna"},
{question: "Which city is home to the White House currently occupied by Donald Trump?", answer: "Washington D.C."},
{question: "Which city can you ride on the BTS or MRT?", answer: "Bangkok"},
{question: "Which city is home to the famous Eiffel Tower?", answer: "Paris"},
{question: "In which city can you walk through Checkpoint Charlie?", answer: "Berlin"},
{question: "Which capital city is also know simply as DF?", answer: "Mexico City"},
{question: "Which city is the current home of the Egyptian temple of Debod?", answer: "Madrid"},
{question: "Which city is home to Hallgrimskirkja?", answer: "Reykjavik"},
{question: "In which city can you find the Ponte Vasco de Gama?", answer: "Lisbon"},
{question: "Which city is home to the famous nightlife district called Itaewon?", answer: "Seoul"},
{question: "What is the Capital of the largest Muslim country in the world?", answer: "Jakarta"},
{question: "In which city can you find the Gold Mask of Tutankhamun?", answer: "Cairo"},
{question: "What city is home to the world famous Colosseum?", answer: "Rome"},
{question: "In which city can you ski on the Holmenkollbakken?", answer: "Oslo"},
{question: "In which city is the headquarters of the European Union?", answer: "Brussels"},
{question: "Which city is the hub of the airline known as KLM?", answer: "Amsterdam"},
{question: "In which city can you find the township of Soweto?", answer: "Johannesburg"},
{question: "In which city can you walk through the Red Square to see the Kremlin?", answer: "Moscow"},
{question: "Which city is located on the western bank of the Rio de la Plata?", answer: "Buenos Aires"},
{question: "Which city is portrayed in the film Black Hawk Down?", answer: "Mogadishu"},
{question: "Which city is home to Etihad Airways?", answer: "Abu Dhabi"},
{question: "Which city is home to the fictional character known as Borat?", answer: "Astana"},
{question: "What is the capital city of the most populous country in the world?", answer: "Beijing"},
{question: "Which capital city is located on the island called Luzon?", answer: "Manila"},
{question: "Which city is located high above the Taedong River?", answer: "Pyongyang"},
{question: "Which city was featured in the film Lost in Translation?", answer: "Tokyo"},
{question: "What is the Capital of Turkey?", answer: "Ankara"},
{question: "In which capital city can you cross the Thames River?", answer: "London"},
{question: "Which capital city is closest to Machu Picchu?", answer: "Lima"},
{question: "Which capital city was home to Fidel Castro?", answer: "Havana"},